Guide to the Department of Manuscripts and Archives, Yale University, Reference Service Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Public services records, 1968-2005; 1997-2005; Accession 2005-A-043
  - Office of Origin call slips [filed by fiscal year returned; within year by YRG number]
    - YRG 4-E, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - YRG 9-C, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - YRG 13-C-01, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - YRG 13-D-01, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - YRG 13-E-01, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - YRG 13-F-01, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - YRG 13-G-01, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - YRG 13-H-01, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - YRG 13-I-01, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - YRG 13-J-01, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - YRG 13-K-01, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - YRG 13-L-01, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - YRG 13-M-01, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - YRG 13-N-01, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - YRG 15, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - YRG 20-F, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - YRG 22-F, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - YRG 25-E, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - YRG 27-I, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - YRG 28-C, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - YRG 29-A, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - YRG 32-B, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 84)
    - YRG 32-H, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 85)
    - YRG 34, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 86)
    - YRG 2-A, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 87)
    - YRG 2-E, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 88)
    - YRG 4-E, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 89)
    - YRG 9-B-6, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 90)
    - YRG 13-C-01, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 91)
    - YRG 13-D-01, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 92)
    - YRG 13-E-01, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 93)
    - YRG 13-F-01, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 94)
    - YRG 13-G-01, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 95)
    - YRG 13-H-01, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 96)
    - YRG 13-J-01, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 97)
    - YRG 13-K-01, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 98)
    - YRG 13-L-01, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 99)
    - YRG 13-M-01, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 100)
    - YRG 13-N-01, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 101)
    - YRG 15-A, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 102)
    - YRG 22-F, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 103)
    - YRG 25-E, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 104)
    - YRG 28-C, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 105)
    - YRG 29-A, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 106)
    - YRG 30-F, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 107)
    - YRG 32-C, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 108)
    - YRG 32-H, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 109)
    - YRG 34-A, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 110)
    - YRG 2-A, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 111)
    - YRG 4-A-16, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 112)
    - YRG 4-E, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 113)
    - YRG 8-B, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 114)
    - YRG 9-C, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 115)
    - YRG 13-C-01, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 116)
    - YRG 13-D-01, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 117)
    - YRG 13-E-01, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 118)
    - YRG 13-F-01, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 119)
    - YRG 13-G-01, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 120)
    - YRG 13-H-01, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 121)
    - YRG 13-I-01, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 122)
    - YRG 13-J-01, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 123)
    - YRG 13-K-01, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 124)
    - YRG 13-L-01, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 125)
    - YRG 13-M-01, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 126)
    - YRG 13-N-01, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 127)
    - YRG 15-C, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 128)
    - YRG 20-F, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 129)
    - YRG 22-F, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 130)
    - YRG 23-F, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 131)
    - YRG 25-E, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 132)
    - YRG 27-B, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 133)
    - YRG 28-A, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 134)
    - YRG 29-A, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 135)
    - YRG 30-F, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 136)
    - YRG 32-B, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 137)
    - YRG 32-H, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 138)
    - YRG 37-A, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 139)
    - YRG 47-E, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 140)
    - YRG 2-A -YRG 9-F, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 141)
    - YRG 13-C -YRG 13-I, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 142)
    - YRG 13-J -YRG 13-N, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 143)
    - YRG 14 -YRG 37, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 144)
    - YRG 2 -YRG 9, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 145)
    - YRG 13-C -YRG 13-G, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 146)
    - YRG 13-H -YRG 13-N, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 147)
    - YRG 14 -YRG 25, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 148)
    - YRG 26 -YRG 37, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 149)
    - YRG 2 -YRG 9, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 150)
    - YRG 13-C -YRG 13-G, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 151)
    - YRG 13-H -YRG 13-N, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 152)
    - YRG 14, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 153)
    - YRG 15-B, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 154)
    - YRG 20-A, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 155)
    - YRG 21-F, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 156)
    - YRG 22-A, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 157)
    - YRG 25-F, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 158)
    - YRG 26, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 159)
    - YRG 28-C, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 160)
    - YRG 32-A, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 161)
    - YRG 32-H, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 162)
    - YRG 34-A, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 163)
    - YRG 37-A, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 164)
    - YRG 46, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 165)
    - YRG 2, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 166)
    - YRG 3-D, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 167)
    - YRG 4-E, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 168)
    - YRG 5-D, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 169)
    - YRG 9-F, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 170)
    - YRG 13-C01, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 171)
    - YRG 13-D-01, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 172)
    - YRG 13-E-01, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 173)
    - YRG 13-F-01, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 174)
    - YRG 13-G-01, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 175)
    - YRG 13-H-01, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 176)
    - YRG 13-I-01, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 177)
    - YRG 13-J-01, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 178)
    - YRG 13-K-01, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 179)
    - YRG 13-L-01, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 180)
    - YRG 13-M-01, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 181)
    - YRG 13-N-01, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 182)
    - YRG 14-B, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 183)
    - YRG 15-C, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 184)
    - YRG 21-F, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 185)
    - YRG 22-F, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 186)
    - YRG 25-E, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 187)
    - YRG 26-F, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 188)
    - YRG 28-F, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 189)
    - YRG 29-F, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 190)
    - YRG 30-F, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 191)
    - YRG 31-F, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 192)
    - YRG 32-E, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 193)
    - YRG 37, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 194)
    - YRG 46-A, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 195)
    - YRG 2, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 196)
    - YRG 3, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 197)
    - YRG 4, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 198)
    - YRG 5, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 199)
    - YRG 9, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 200)
    - YRG 13-D -YRG 13-J, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 201)
    - YRG 13-K -YRG 13-N, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 202)
    - YRG 14, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 203)
    - YRG 15, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 204)
    - YRG 19-H, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 205)
    - YRG 21, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 206)
    - YRG 22, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 207)
    - YRG 25, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 208)
    - YRG 26, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 209)
    - YRG 29, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 210)
    - YRG 30, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 211)
    - YRG 32, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 212)
  - Permissions to use restricted materials, 1984-2004 (Box 3, Folder 213 - 216)
  - Patron sign-in register sheets
    - 1997 Jul -Sep (Box 3, Folder 217)
    - 1997 Oct -Dec (Box 3, Folder 218)
    - 1998 Jan -Mar (Box 3, Folder 219)
    - 1998 Apr -Jun (Box 3, Folder 220)
    - 1998 Jul -Sep (Box 4, Folder 221)
    - 1998 Oct -Dec (Box 4, Folder 222)
    - 1999 Jan -Mar (Box 4, Folder 223)
    - 1999 Apr -Jun (Box 4, Folder 224)
    - 1999 Jul -Sep (Box 4, Folder 225)
    - 1999 Oct -Dec (Box 4, Folder 226)
    - 2000 Mar (Box 4, Folder 227)
    - 2000 Jun (Box 4, Folder 228)
    - 2001 Feb -Jun (Box 4, Folder 229)
    - 2001 Jul -Sep (Box 4, Folder 230)
    - 2001 Oct -Dec (Box 4, Folder 231)
    - 2002 Jan -Mar (Box 4, Folder 232)
    - 2002 Apr -Jun (Box 4, Folder 233)
    - 2002 Jul -Sep (Box 4, Folder 234)
    - 2002 Oct -Dec (Box 4, Folder 235)
    - 2003 Jan -Mar (Box 4, Folder 236)
    - 2003 Apr -Jun (Box 4, Folder 237)
    - 2003 Jul -Sep (Box 4, Folder 238)
    - 2003 Oct -Dec (Box 4, Folder 239)
    - 2004 Jan -Mar (Box 4, Folder 240)
    - 2004 Apr -Jun (Box 4, Folder 241)
    - 2004 Jul -Sep (Box 4, Folder 242)
    - 2004 Oct -Dec (Box 4, Folder 243)
    - 2005 Jan -Mar (Box 4, Folder 244)
    - 2005 Apr -Jun (Box 4, Folder 245)
  - Reprographics order forms [filed by fiscal year, then alphabetically by requester surname; for earlier years, reproduction orders from publications and microfilm were separated from manuscript/archival reproductions]
    - A -L publications and microfilm copies, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 246)
    - M -Z publications and microfilm copies, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 247)
    - A, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 248)
    - B, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 249)
    - C, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 250)
    - D, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 251)
    - E, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 252)
    - F, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 253)
    - G, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 254)
    - H, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 255)
    - I, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 256)
    - J, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 257)
    - K, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 258)
    - L, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 259)
    - Mc, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 260)
    - M, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 261)
    - N, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 262)
    - O, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 263)
    - P, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 264)
    - Q, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 265)
    - R, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 266)
    - S, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 267)
    - T, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 268)
    - U, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 269)
    - V, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 270)
    - W, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 271)
    - Y, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 272)
    - Z, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 273)
    - A -Z publications and microfilm copies, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 274)
    - A, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 275)
    - B, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 276)
    - C, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 277)
    - D, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 278)
    - E, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 279)
    - F, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 280)
    - G, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 281)
    - H, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 282 - 283)
    - I, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 284)
    - J, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 285)
    - K, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 286)
    - L, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 287)
    - Mc, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 288)
    - M, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 289)
    - N, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 290)
    - O, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 291)
    - P, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 292)
    - R, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 293)
    - S, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 294)
    - T, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 295)
    - U, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 296)
    - V, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 297)
    - W, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 298)
    - X, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 299)
    - Y, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 300)
    - Z, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 301)
    - A -L publications and microfilm copies, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 302)
    - M -Z publications and microfilm copies, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 303)
    - A, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 304)
    - B, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 305)
    - C, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 306)
    - D, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 307)
    - E, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 308)
    - F, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 309)
    - G, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 310)
    - H, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 311)
    - I, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 312)
    - J, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 313)
    - K, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 314)
    - L, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 315)
    - Mc, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 316)
    - M, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 317)
    - N -O, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 318)
    - P -Q, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 319)
    - R, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 320)
    - S, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 321)
    - T, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 322)
    - U -V, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 323)
    - W, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 324)
    - Y -Z, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 325)
    - A -B, 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 326)
    - C -D, 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 327)
    - E -G, 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 328)
    - H -J, 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 329)
    - K -L, 2000-2001 (Box 7, Folder 330)
    - M -N, 2000-2001 (Box 7, Folder 331)
    - O -P, 2000-2001 (Box 7, Folder 332)
    - R, 2000-2001 (Box 7, Folder 333)
    - S, 2000-2001 (Box 7, Folder 334)
    - T -Z, 2000-2001 (Box 7, Folder 335)
    - A -B, 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 336)
    - C -D, 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 337)
    - E -G, 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 338)
    - H -J, 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 339)
    - K -L, 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 340)
    - M -N, 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 341)
    - O -P, 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 342)
    - R, 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 343)
    - S, 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 344)
    - T -Z, 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 345)
    - A -B, 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 346)
    - C -D, 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 347)
    - E -G, 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 348)
    - H -J, 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 349)
    - K -L, 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 350)
    - M -N, 2002-2003 (Box 8, Folder 351)
    - O -Q, 2002-2003 (Box 8, Folder 352)
    - R, 2002-2003 (Box 8, Folder 353)
    - S, 2002-2003 (Box 8, Folder 354)
    - T -Z, 2002-2003 (Box 8, Folder 355)
    - A, 2003-2004 (Box 8, Folder 356)
    - B, 2003-2004 (Box 8, Folder 357)
    - C, 2003-2004 (Box 8, Folder 358)
    - D, 2003-2004 (Box 8, Folder 359)
    - E, 2003-2004 (Box 8, Folder 360)
    - F, 2003-2004 (Box 8, Folder 361)
    - G, 2003-2004 (Box 8, Folder 362)
    - H -I, 2003-2004 (Box 8, Folder 363)
    - J -K, 2003-2004 (Box 8, Folder 364)
    - L, 2003-2004 (Box 8, Folder 365)
    - M, 2003-2004 (Box 8, Folder 366)
    - N -P, 2003-2004 (Box 8, Folder 367)
    - R, 2003-2004 (Box 8, Folder 368)
    - S -T, 2003-2004 (Box 8, Folder 369)
    - U -Z, 2003-2004 (Box 8, Folder 370)
    - A, 2004-2005 (Box 8, Folder 371)
    - B, 2004-2005 (Box 8, Folder 372)
    - C, 2004-2005 (Box 8, Folder 373)
    - D, 2004-2005 (Box 8, Folder 374)
    - E, 2004-2005 (Box 8, Folder 375)
    - F, 2004-2005 (Box 8, Folder 376)
    - G, 2004-2005 (Box 8, Folder 377)
    - H, 2004-2005 (Box 8, Folder 378)
    - I - J, 2004-2005 (Box 8, Folder 379)
    - K, 2004-2005 (Box 8, Folder 380)
    - L, 2004-2005 (Box 8, Folder 381)
    - M, 2004-2005 (Box 8, Folder 382)
    - N - Q, 2004-2005 (Box 8, Folder 383)
    - R, 2004-2005 (Box 8, Folder 384)
    - S, 2004-2005 (Box 8, Folder 385)
    - T - V, 2004-2005 (Box 8, Folder 386)
    - W -Z, 2004-2005 (Box 8, Folder 387)
  - Reference correspondence [filed by fiscal year, then alphabetically by requester's surname]
    - Abe -Ald, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 388)
    - Ale -Ayr, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 389)
    - Bab -Bar, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 390)
    - Bas -Ben, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 391)
    - Ber -Bjo, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 392)
    - Bla -Bow, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 393)
    - Bra -Buh, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 394)
    - Bun -Byr, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 395)
    - Cac -Car, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 396)
    - Cas -Chu, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 397)
    - Cie -Coo, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 398)
    - Cor -Cur, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 399)
    - Dal -Dem, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 400)
    - Den -Dok, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 401)
    - Dou -Dye, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 402)
    - Ece -Eva, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 403)
    - Fal -Fit, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 404)
    - Fla -Fun, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 405)
    - Gad -Ges, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 406)
    - Gif -Goy, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 407)
    - Gra -Gut, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 408)
    - Haa -Ham, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 409)
    - Han -Hay, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 410)
    - Hea -Hit, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 411)
    - Hod -Hou, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 412)
    - How -Hys, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 413)
    - Ich -Jar, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 414)
    - Jen -Jud, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 415)
    - Kas -Kis, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 416)
    - Kla -Kop, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 417)
    - Kor -Kut, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 418)
    - Lab -Lem, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 419)
    - Leo -Lin, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 420)
    - Lip -Lyn, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 421)
    - McA -McM, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 422)
    - Mab -May, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 423)
    - Mar -Mik, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 424)
    - Mil -Mon, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 425)
    - Moo -Msu, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 426)
    - Mul -Mye, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 427)
    - Nab -Nus, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 428)
    - Oak -Owe, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 429)
    - Pak -Peo, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 430)
    - Per -Por, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 431)
    - Pot -Qui, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 432)
    - Rab -Riz, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 433)
    - Roa -Rom, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 434)
    - Ror -Ryg, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 435)
    - Saa -Say, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 436)
    - Scha -Schw, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 437)
    - Scu -Sin, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 438)
    - Sir -Son, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 439)
    - Sou -Sti, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 440)
    - Sto -Sza, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 441)
    - Tab -Thr, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 442)
    - Til -Tys, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 443)
    - Ujh -Vuo, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 444)
    - Wag -War, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 445)
    - Was -Wes, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 446)
    - Wet -Wil, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 447)
    - Win -Wyl, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 448)
    - Yag -Zub, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 449)
    - Ab -Am, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 450)
    - An -Av, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 451)
    - Ba -Bel, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 452)
    - Ben -Bo, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 453)
    - Br, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 454)
    - Bu -By, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 455)
    - Cab -Cep, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 456)
    - Cha -Cli, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 457)
    - Cob -Cur, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 458)
    - Dab -Des, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 459)
    - Dew -Dya, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 460)
    - E, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 461)
    - F, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 462)
    - Gab -Gou, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 463)
    - Gra -Gut, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 464)
    - Hab -Hen, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 465)
    - Her -Hyn, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 466)
    - I -J, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 467)
    - Kab -Kes, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 468)
    - Kib -Kwe, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 469)
    - Lad -Ley, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 470)
    - Lie -Lys, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 471)
    - McA -Mad, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 472)
    - Mag -Mey, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 473)
    - Mic -Mur, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 474)
    - N -O, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 475)
    - Pac -Per, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 476)
    - Pet -Put, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 477)
    - Q, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 478)
    - Raa -Rob, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 479)
    - Roc -Rya, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 480)
    - Sab -Shu, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 481)
    - Sie -Sri, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 482)
    - Sta -Swe, 2001-2002 (Box 13, Folder 483)
    - T, 2001-2002 (Box 13, Folder 484)
    - U, 2001-2002 (Box 13, Folder 485)
    - V, 2001-2002 (Box 13, Folder 486)
    - Wag -Wet, 2001-2002 (Box 13, Folder 487)
    - Wha -Wyn, 2001-2002 (Box 13, Folder 488)
    - Y -Z, 2001-2002 (Box 13, Folder 489)
    - Aa -Ak, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 490)
    - Al -Az, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 491)
    - Bab -Bar, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 492)
    - Bas -Bew, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 493)
    - Bib -Bix, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 494)
    - Bla -Boy, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 495)
    - Bra -Buh, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 496)
    - Bul -Bry, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 497)
    - Cab -Cap, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 498)
    - Car -Caz, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 499)
    - Ch, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 500)
    - Ci -Cl, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 501)
    - Cod -Coo, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 502)
    - Cor -Cz, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 503)
    - Da -Del, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 504)
    - Den -Do, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 505)
    - Dr -Dw, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 506)
    - E, 2002-2003 (Box 14, Folder 507)
    - Fak -Fit, 2002-2003 (Box 14, Folder 508)
    - Fla -Fun, 2002-2003 (Box 14, Folder 509)
    - Gab -Ge, 2002-2003 (Box 14, Folder 510)
    - Gi -Go, 2002-2003 (Box 14, Folder 511)
    - Gr -Gu, 2002-2003 (Box 14, Folder 512)
    - Hac -Ham, 2002-2003 (Box 14, Folder 513)
    - Han -Haz, 2002-2003 (Box 14, Folder 514)
    - He -Hi, 2002-2003 (Box 14, Folder 515)
    - Hoa -Hou, 2002-2003 (Box 14, Folder 516)
    - How -Hy, 2002-2003 (Box 14, Folder 517)
    - I, 2002-2003 (Box 14, Folder 518)
    - Ja -Je, 2002-2003 (Box 14, Folder 519)
    - Jo -Ju, 2002-2003 (Box 14, Folder 520)
    - Ka -Ki, 2002-2003 (Box 14, Folder 521)
    - Kl -Kol, 2002-2003 (Box 14, Folder 522)
    - Kot -Kr, 2002-2003 (Box 14, Folder 523)
    - La- Leg, 2002-2003 (Box 14, Folder 524)
    - Leo -Lin, 2002-2003 (Box 14, Folder 525)
    - Lip -Ly, 2002-2003 (Box 14, Folder 526)
    - Mc, 2002-2003 (Box 14, Folder 527)
    - Ma, 2002-2003 (Box 14, Folder 528)
    - Me -Mik, 2002-2003 (Box 15, Folder 529)
    - Mil -Mon, 2002-2003 (Box 15, Folder 530)
    - Moo -Mos, 2002-2003 (Box 15, Folder 531)
    - Mu -My, 2002-2003 (Box 15, Folder 532)
    - N, 2002-2003 (Box 15, Folder 533)
    - O, 2002-2003 (Box 15, Folder 534)
    - Pac -Pep, 2002-2003 (Box 15, Folder 535)
    - Per -Pi, 2002-2003 (Box 15, Folder 536)
    - Pot -Q, 2002-2003 (Box 15, Folder 537)
    - Ra -Rit, 2002-2003 (Box 15, Folder 538)
    - Rob -Ron, 2002-2003 (Box 15, Folder 539)
    - Ros -Ry, 2002-2003 (Box 15, Folder 540)
    - Saa -Sav, 2002-2003 (Box 15, Folder 541)
    - Sca -Sco, 2002-2003 (Box 15, Folder 542)
    - Se -Si, 2002-2003 (Box 15, Folder 543)
    - Sk -Son, 2002-2003 (Box 15, Folder 544)
    - Sor -Sti, 2002-2003 (Box 15, Folder 545)
    - Sto -Sy, 2002-2003 (Box 15, Folder 546)
    - Ta -Th, 2002-2003 (Box 15, Folder 547)
    - Ti -Ty, 2002-2003 (Box 15, Folder 548)
    - U -V, 2002-2003 (Box 15, Folder 549)
    - Wa, 2002-2003 (Box 15, Folder 550)
    - Web -Wie, 2002-2003 (Box 15, Folder 551)
    - Wil -Wu, 2002-2003 (Box 15, Folder 552)
    - Y -Z, 2002-2003 (Box 15, Folder 553)
    - Ab -Al, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 554)
    - Am -Ay, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 555)
    - Bab -Bar, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 556)
    - Bea -Bet, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 557)
    - Bh -Bl, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 558)
    - Bod -Boy, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 559)
    - Bra -Bry, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 560)
    - Bu -By, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 561)
    - Cad -Car, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 562)
    - Cas -Chu, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 563)
    - Cia -Cop, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 564)
    - Cor -Cut, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 565)
    - Dah -Dha, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 566)
    - Dia -Dow, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 567)
    - Dra -Duz, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 568)
    - E, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 569)
    - Fa -Fe, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 570)
    - Fie -Ful, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 571)
    - Gab -Gay, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 572)
    - Geb -Gil, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 573)
    - Gim -Gou, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 574)
    - Gra -Gut, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 575)
    - Haa -Han, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 576)
    - Har -Haz, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 577)
    - Hea -Hli, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 578)
    - Hob -Hou, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 579)
    - How -Hur, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 580)
    - Ill -Isr, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 581)
    - Jan -Jew, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 582)
    - Joc -Jur, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 583)
    - Kaa -Ker, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 584)
    - Kha -Kli, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 585)
    - Kni -Kwo, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 586)
    - Lad -Law, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 587)
    - Lea -Liu, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 588)